<resources>
    // app wide
    <string name="app_name" translatable="false">Lorolingo</string>

    // activity choice instructions
    <string name="language_instruction_title">Choose a language to learn</string>
    <string name="category_instruction_title">Choose a category to improve</string>

    // languages
    <string name="english_language">English</string>
    <string name="spanish_language">Spanish</string>
    <string name="french_language">French</string>
    <string name="german_language">German</string>
    <string name="portuguese_language">Portuguese</string>
    <string name="italian_language">Italian</string>

    // categories
    <string name="numbers_category">Numbers</string>
    <string name="alphabet_category">Alphabet</string>
    <string name="fruit_category">Fruit</string>
    <string name="vegetables_category">Vegetables</string>
    <string name="animals_category">Animals</string>
    <string name="jobs_category">Jobs</string>
    <string name="transport_category">Transport</string>
    <string name="household_category">Household</string>

    // action button names
    <string name="about_action_button_text">About</string>
    <string name="faq_action_button_text">FAQ</string>
    <string name="credit_action_button_text">Credit</string>

    // settings
    <string name="about_text">
        <![CDATA[
            <p>Welcome to Lorolingo! 🌍</p>
            <br/>
            <p>Lorolingo is a language learning app designed to help children learn vocabulary in a foreign language.
            The app uses children\'s natural ability to hear and distinguish the sounds of foreign languages by linking
            them with everyday objects.</p>
            <br/>
            <p>Lorolingo was originally designed with parents bringing up a child in a foreign country in mind,
            but it is equally useful for bilingual parents or parents who wish to give their child a head-start in a foreign language.</p>
            <br/>
            <p>Lorolingo is free to use, ad-free and always will be. However, if you would like to support additional features or help me
            with on-going maintenance you can do one of the following:
            </p><br/>

            - watch a short advertisement by clicking the in-app ❤️ icon.
            <br/>
            - buy me a coffee by clicking right here 👉 buymeacoff.ee/jonathancoffee
            <br/><br/>
            Happy learning!
            <br/>
            Jonathan
         ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="faq_text">
        <![CDATA[
            <h6>What is Lorolingo?</h6>
            <p>
            Lorolingo is a language learning app designed to help children learn vocabulary in a foreign language.
            The app uses children\'s natural ability to hear and distinguish the sounds of foreign languages by linking
            them with everyday objects
            </p>
            <br/>
            <h6>How can my child use Lorolingo?</h6>
            <p>
            Lorolingo can be used in two ways:
            <br/>
            1) By passing the device to your child, having first selected a language, and allowing them to play and choose images independently.
            <br/>
            2) By selecting a language and interacting with your child. Ask them questions in the target language about the images that appear, and watch them learn!
            </p>
            <br/>
            <h6>Why is the app free?</h6>
            <p>
            Lorolingo started as a side-project of mine with the aim of improving my development skills and filling a gap that
            currently exists in the Android app market - that is, good quality learning resources for parents trying to teach their children a foreign language.
            </p>
            <br/>
            <h6>How can I contribute and support the app?</h6>
            <p>
            The app can be supported by pressing the in-app ❤️ icon and watching a short advertisement, or by buying me a coffee by clicking right here 👉 buymeacoff.ee/jonathancoffee
            </p>
            <br/>
            <h6>I have a feature request, how can I let you know?</h6>
            <p>
            Features such new categories, general improvements, etc., can be communicated by sending an email to:
            hellolorolingo@gmail.com
            </p>
            <br/>
            <h6>There\'s a problem with the app, how can I let you know?</h6>
            <p>
            All problems such as translation problems, in-app issues, etc. can be communicated by sending an email to:
            hellolorolingo@gmail.com
            </p>
            <br/>
         ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="coffee_text_title">
        Your support is important!
    </string>

    <string name="coffee_text">
        Building and maintaining an app is tough...
        but you can help keep me energized with coffee
        by watching a short advertisement!
    </string>

    <string name="credit_text">
        <![CDATA[
            <h6>Image credit</h6>
            <br/>
            <p>Country flag icons made by Freepik from www.flaticon.com and distributed under the Flaticon Basic Licence</p><br/>
            <p>Number icons made by Freepik from www.flaticon.com and distributed under the Flaticon Basic Licence</p><br/>
            <p>Alphabet icons made by Twitter from www.flaticon.com and distributed under CC 3.0 BY</p><br/>
            <p>Fruit icons made by Freepik from www.flaticon.com and distributed under the Flaticon Basic Licence</p><br/>
            <p>Vegetables icons made by Freepik from www.flaticon.com and distributed under the Flaticon Basic Licence</p><br/>
            <p>Animal icons made by Freepik from www.flaticon.com and distributed under the Flaticon Basic Licence</p><br/>
            <p>Job icons made by Freepik from www.flaticon.com and distributed under the Flaticon Basic Licence</p><br/>
            <p>Transport icons made by Freepik from www.flaticon.com and distributed under the Flaticon Basic Licence</p><br/>
            <p>Household icons made by Freepik from www.flaticon.com and distributed under the Flaticon Basic Licence</p><br/>
         ]]>
    </string>

    // other misc
    <string name = "error_text">
        oops, there\'s been an error!
    </string>

    <string name = "video_ad_finish_message">
        Thanks for your support! :)
    </string>

    <string name = "video_ad_left_ad_message">
        You left the app before watching the ad :(
    </string>

    <string name = "video_ad_not_loading">
        "Oops... the ad can't be loaded right now, please try again later!"
    </string>

    <string name = "ok_alert_button">
        Ok
    </string>

    <string name = "no_alert_button">
        No thanks
    </string>

    <string name = "tts_voice_data_prompt">
        TTS voice data must be installed in order to use the chosen language
    </string>

    <string name = "tts_not_initialised_msg">
        Please try again in a few seconds... the text-to-speech engine is not ready yet
    </string>

    <string name = "tts_voice_data_installing_msg">
        TTS data is not available and will be downloaded in the background. Please try again in a few moments
    </string>
</resources>
